<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="@drawable/bcl"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    tools:context=".News_feed">

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="398dp"
        android:layout_height="715dp"
        android:layout_marginStart="8dp"
        android:layout_marginLeft="8dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
        android:layout_marginEnd="8dp"
        android:layout_marginRight="8dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
        app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="1.0"
        app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
        app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.901">

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/tvnews1"
            android:layout_width="385dp"
            android:layout_height="637dp"
            android:layout_marginStart="8dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="8dp"
            android:layout_marginEnd="8dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="8dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
            android:text="The Siemens digital factory twin:\n\n\t Located in a town in
Bavaria, Germany, the Siemens Electronics Works Amberg manufactures a range of precision
products like programmable logic controllers and human-machine interfaces. The site is a
world-class digital factory, pioneering digitalization initiatives to drive efficiencies and
shorten time to market.\n\n\tIndeed, without increasing the size of the production area –
10,000 square meters – and with almost no change in staffing levels, the factory has increased
its production capacity thirteen-fold since it first opened in 1989. These efficiency gains
have also increased production flexibility, enabling the factory to manufacture over 1000
product variants per day and one product per second.\n\n\tSiemens Electronics Works Amberg
continues to pioneer innovations in the digital factory; in 2018 they completed a project with
NavVis to implement a fully immersive digital twin of the indoor space.\n\n\t“With NavVis
IndoorViewer, I have my factory in my pocket,” says Thomas Meier, Head of Technology
Excellence at Siemens Electronics Works.\n\n
The need for accurate data and documentation:\n\n\tThe challenge with the Siemens Amberg
factory, as with all modern manufacturing facilities, is to provide multiple stakeholders with
up-to-the-minute information about the current condition of the site.\n\n\tFactory planners
need accurate data and context for assembly line relocation projects, whether it’s for initial
scoping or implementation when tendering the necessary suppliers. Keeping track and accurately
documenting the multiple incremental shop floor changes to respond to new market demands can
be incredibly challenging.\n\n\t“We have to continuously relocate machines or assembly
equipment to other factories,explains Meier.\n\n\tSiemens also regularly invites potential
customers to visit Amberg, running over 400 factory tours a year. For safety reasons and to

avoid disrupting production schedules, tours are conducted on a balcony above the shop floor.
With only a birds-eye view of the facility, however, customers don’t have the opportunity to
take a closer look at specific machines.\n\n\tWe’re doing our guided tours for our visitors
from the balcony so they can have a full overview of our production,” says Meier.0 “But in
some cases, it's also necessary to go to the details.\n\nA speedy solution with the NavVis
M6\n\n\tEnter NavVis. Siemens approached us to investigate how our digital factory solution
could empower them to build a virtual replica of their factory space, so they could unlock
greater operational efficiency and improve collaboration between factory stakeholders
globally. \n\n\tThe first step was to generate a point cloud of their production floor quickly
and without fuss; the NavVis M6 Indoor Mobile Mapping System was used to scan 10,000 sqm in a
single day, with minimal interruption to operations.\n\n\tAnd when the team at Siemens saw a
virtual replica of their facility from within NavVis IndoorViewer, the value of the NavVis
digital factory solution truly became apparent.\n\n\tCombining accurate point cloud data with
360 ̊ panoramic images, NavVis IndoorViewer provides an immersive 3D walkthrough; building
stakeholders can instantly review the “as-is” state of the factory from any web
browser.\n\nMore efficient assembly planning, factory tours, and more\n\n\tAccording to Thomas
Meier, Siemens now use their factory digital twin of the Electronics Works Amberg for several
different use-cases – and are exploring potential applications for the future.
“In the past, colleagues have to come to me to Amberg and see the production equipment, so
that they get an overview or an impression how it looks like,” Meier says."
            android:textColor="#0C0505"
            android:textSize="22sp"
            app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
            app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
            app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
            app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
            app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="1.0" />
    </ScrollView>
</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>